1
00:00:00,0 --> 00:00:00,200
Start; Clip_00000

2
00:00:03,837 --> 00:00:04,37
Atomic_Clock; 7:23:03

3
00:01:35,528 --> 00:01:35,729
Start; Pre_Trial

4
00:01:35,895 --> 00:01:36,96
803; S; G5; 7; 8

5
00:04:38,378 --> 00:04:38,578
End; Pre_Trial

6
00:04:50,957 --> 00:04:51,157
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 3; 5

7
00:04:56,796 --> 00:04:56,996
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 3; 7

8
00:05:04,571 --> 00:05:04,771
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 3; 7

9
00:05:12,512 --> 00:05:12,712
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 3; 7

10
00:05:17,183 --> 00:05:17,384
Start; Female_Playback; # Start time approximate (cannot hear playback on video)

11
00:05:33,967 --> 00:05:34,167
End; Female_Playback; # End time approximate (cannot hear playback on video)

12
00:05:49,683 --> 00:05:49,883
Start; Female_Approach

13
00:06:56,549 --> 00:06:56,750
803; SR; 320; NA; H4; 3; 4

14
00:07:08,895 --> 00:07:09,95
803; SR; 35; NA; H4; 3; 5

15
00:07:18,71 --> 00:07:18,271
803; SR; 320; NA; H4; 3; 5

16
00:07:27,681 --> 00:07:27,881
803; SR; 80; NA; H4; 3; 5

17
00:08:00,914 --> 00:08:01,114
End; Female_Approach

18
00:08:04,317 --> 00:08:04,517
Start; Phase_1

19
00:09:49,723 --> 00:09:49,923
803; SR; 340; NA; G4; 8; 9 ~

20
00:09:56,830 --> 00:09:57,30
803; SR; 30; NA; G5; 8; 5 ~

21
00:10:02,902 --> 00:10:03,103
803; SR; 0; NA; G5; 7; 5 ~

22
00:10:10,810 --> 00:10:11,11
803; SR; 0; NA; G5; 7; 6 ~

23
00:10:17,550 --> 00:10:17,751
803; SR; 270; NA; G5; 6; 3 ~

24
00:12:24,811 --> 00:12:25,11
803; SR; 110; NA; H4; 0; 5

25
00:12:32,318 --> 00:12:32,519
803; SR; 30; NA; H4; 0; 5

26
00:12:39,659 --> 00:12:39,859
803; SR; 300; NA; H4; 0; 6

27
00:12:48,802 --> 00:12:49,2
803; SR; 290; NA; H4; 0; 6

28
00:14:04,911 --> 00:14:05,111
End; Phase_1

29
00:14:13,720 --> 00:14:13,920
Start; Female_Exit

30
00:16:06,966 --> 00:16:07,167
End; Female_Exit

31
00:16:11,204 --> 00:16:11,404
Start; Post_Trial; # Possibly hens clucking near road during post-trial?

32
00:17:54,274 --> 00:17:54,474
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 2; 4

33
00:18:00,413 --> 00:18:00,613
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 2; 4

34
00:18:09,456 --> 00:18:09,656
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 1; 4

35
00:18:24,170 --> 00:18:24,371
803; SR; NA; NA; H4; 0; 6

36
00:19:12,85 --> 00:19:12,285
End; Post_Trial

